estibot.com 2008-11-21

# Bulk Availability Check and MULTI Whois Tool by EstiBot.com

**The following is the requisite privacy policy jargon. In short, there are cookies and the like, but I will never give your personal information to anyone without your explicit permission**

**Privacy Policy**

Updated Sep/02/2008 

**Privacy Policy Table Of Contents:**   

* Our Commitment To Privacy
* The Information We Collect
* How We Use Information
* Our Commitment To Data Security
* Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
* How To Access Or Correct Your Information
* How To Contact Us
* Cookies
* Log Information
* Affiliated Sites
* Links
* Other Sites

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Estibot.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive benefits. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name   
Address   
Email address   
Phone number   
Paypal E-mail address 

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive and to send our sporadic newsletter, which will only be sent when users need to be informed of changes in the website. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

You can register with our website if you would like to receive subscription benefits. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals from a certain country visited a certain area on our website, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in to your account and selecting ->My Account. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at info@estibot.com. We answer all emails within 48 hours (usually much faster). 

**Cookies**

When you visit Estibot.com, we send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. This is called a PHP Session ID cookie, and it is essential for the technical functions that Estibot needs to perform your requested operations. If you are a subscriber, Estibot will also set a cookie that identifies your browser and keeps you logged on to your account services. If you visit our partner websites, such as through affiliate links, we may set a cookie to inform our partner that you are arriving from Estibot.com. 

**Log information**

When you access your Estibot.com subscription services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit one of the pages on Estibot.com. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. This is for security purposes - it's how we monitor for fraudulent user activity and fraudulent payment activity. 

**Affiliated sites**

We offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. 

**Links**

Estibot may present links in a format (redirected URLs) that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our services and advertising. 

**Other sites**

This Privacy Policy applies to Estibot.com services only. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.
